---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:27:11 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=65f5df3c332eb85b564f6a973aeb12b4; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How
        many planets are in our Solar System?","correct_answer":"Eight","incorrect_answers":["Nine","Seven","Ten"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What was the
        name of the cancelled sequel of Team Fortress?","correct_answer":"Team Fortress
        2: Brotherhood of Arms","incorrect_answers":["Team Fortress 2: Desert Mercenaries","Team
        Fortress 2: Operation Gear Grinder","Team Fortress 2: Return to Classic"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Studio
        Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf
        Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game
        &quot;Overwatch,&quot; what are the names of the two Australian criminals
        from the Junkers faction?","correct_answer":"Junkrat and Roadhog","incorrect_answers":["Roadrat
        and Junkhog","Ana and Pharah","McCree and Deadeye"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Musicals & Theatres","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In
        Shakespeare&#039;s play Julius Caesar, Caesar&#039;s last words were...","correct_answer":"Et
        tu, Brute? ","incorrect_answers":["Iacta alea est!","Vidi, vini, vici.","Aegri
        somnia vana."]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kanye
        West&#039;s &quot;Gold Digger&quot; featured which Oscar-winning actor?","correct_answer":"Jamie
        Foxx","incorrect_answers":["Alec Baldwin","Dwayne Johnson"," Bruce Willis"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In
        the 2012 animated film &quot;Wolf Children&quot;, what are the names of the
        wolf children?","correct_answer":"Ame &amp; Yuki","incorrect_answers":["Hana
        &amp; Yuki","Ame &amp; Hana","Chuck &amp; Anna"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Former
        president Theodore Roosevelt (1900-1908)  ran for another term under the Progressive
        Party in 1912.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the
        hardest possible difficulty in &quot;Deus Ex: Mankind Divided&quot;?","correct_answer":"I
        Never Asked For This","incorrect_answers":["Nightmare","Extreme","Guru"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which character
        was introduced to the Super Smash Bros franchise in Super Smash Bros Melee?","correct_answer":"Sheik","incorrect_answers":["Samus","Lucas","Mega
        Man"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:27:12 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
